PRERNA KANGTANI

2/32 Bohra Market, Ichalkaranji • 8767322683 • prean14012003@gmail.com

PROFILE

I'm a seasoned web developer in creating user-friendly and visually appealing websites. I specialize in utilizing HTML, CSS, JavaScript, php and Next JS 14 to craft cutting-edge solutions that exceed client expectations and drive online success.

WORK EXPERIENCE

UI UX Developer, TF Strategies Pvt. Ltd.

Jan 2024 - Present

- Introduced with Next JS 14 and made static websites.
- Connected with clients, discussed designs for website implemented in Figma and then developed accordingly using next js or php.
- · Adding payment gateways and database to make website dynamic.

Web Developer, Acmegrade

Jun 2023 - Aug 2023

- Internship training program learned to make websites using HTML, CSS, Javascript, php
- Used Database to store users credentials using SQL and xampp.
- Made e-commerce project Furni where all teachings have been implemented.

Research Associate, Ameliorate Digital Consultancy Pvt. Ltd.

Sep 2022 - May 2023

- Learned how SEO works and made content accordingly.
- Made several research for seveal markets and made overall report which can be helpful for companies working in that specific market.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Application

Sep 2021 - July 2024

Amity University Online

- Got certifications in Advanced Excel, Professional and Life Skills
- Project on "Automation of Research Report". using Java OOP

HSC Boards-EMHS Jr. College DKTE

2021

93%

SSC Boards- New Millennium Public School

2019

86%

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Technical Skills: Next JS 14, React, HTML, CSS, Javascript, php, C, C++
- Languages: English, Hindi
- Certifications: Advance in Excel, Professional and Life Skills, Data Structures using C and C++, Web and Mobile Designer UI UX.